There's a mythological figure there that...
from Trás-os-Montes, which is called Trasgo, that is
associated to the death of children
those children that die and
instead of becoming
ghost, they become the Trasgo
Basically, they are responsible for
stealing the lighters
when we are not looking
so when we look for our
lighters, it's because the Trasgo stole them
I partially agree.
for me it's the socks.
Sound wise, (our band) is the equivalent of using
soy instead of meat to make
spaghetti bolognese, sometimes
it works well, sometimes it tastes fine,
It depends a lot. Sometimes
it turns out good, sometimes it doesn't
Jesus Lizard was an influence before
not so much now, since we
We started to listen
more extreme things and wanted to
go a bit in that direction,
but above all, it only worked out because
we are all friends, above all.
Some of the folks learnt how to play
instruments once they were in the band.
It's interesting, for instance, I like
groovy music, but still noisy,
João likes metal,
standard metal, maybe more to the progressive side.
Costa likes everything that is goofy.
Ricardo, what is your inspiration?
Noisy and deconstructed things
it's cool
I believe you too are the same
as Ricardo.
It only worked out because we got together
and mixed our influences
and started to make music
Aliás, este concerto acho que refletiu um
it only works out since
João and I are looking at each other
doing the rhythm and the rest of the folks are
whatever it pleases them.
Basically the objective today was
we always have a theme and today's
although I don't think people got it
but basically,
Israeli forces are trying to summon
ancient and medieval philosophers to create
a kind of book of destruction.
E o nosso objetivo era meio que parar
isso, porque eles estão a usar a
inteligência artificial.
E pronto, por isso temos que juntar-nos e
ser mais fortes do que estas forças,
exteriores a nós.
E nós quisemos ao máximo que apesar de
ser uma música bastante agressiva, que
também que nós sejamos com vontade de
tocar e por isso estar
confortáveis, por exemplo,
para o Costa é usar chinelos, para mim e
para o João estar com a cara maquilhada,
para o Diogo é ser o Diogo.
E pronto, acho que é só isso.
Minha banda favorita do Porto agora é a
banda "humilde", também uma banda do Stop,
deviam checar, é muito, muito fixe.
Olha, Vaixaxinado, tá, Vaixaxinado
tudo junto, vai-xa, x,
tá numa compilação do bandcamp,
Unsound, Sounds of Porto.
Eles têm lá uma cena chamada,
Pneumacatacumba, foi feita na sala,
onde nós ensaiamos do Stop é algo
que nos diz muito,
sobretudo aqui na cidade do Porto,
eles têm muito movimento underground e tá
publicado em vinil também.
Traumático Desmame, se não conhecem acho
os Tradição de Lisboa, eles já não são
uma banda, mas se calhar com
se o pessoal for ouvir
eles voltam a ser uma banda, mas...
uma cena de hip hop, mesmo mega frito.
Vou ser um bocadinho mais mainstream que
estes manos e dizer Bizarro Locomotiva
que é das minhas
principais influências musicais.